

Applicant for:

iOS Developer (Swift) Uptp 2000\$

Dr.JOY 25 February 2020

TRAN VAN HAN

☑ b.x9.gaming@gmail.com

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Note from ITviec: TRAN VAN HAN skipped the cover letter.



TRAN VAN HAN

SENIOR IOS/MOBILE DEVELOPER

Professional Skills

- Over $8\ years$ of experience in the area of software development for mobiles and web, which includes understanding requirement specification, working on software design, coding, testing, and maintenance.
- Skilled in developing APIs for middleware Framework modules for mobile platforms using Objective C, Swift
 - Experienced in working on nodejs /npm/typescript /docker /
- relational database postgresSQL / redis
- Experienced in working on Swagger API Document/ Swagger codegen
- Experienced in working on iOS platforms and frameworks and customizing it as per requirements.
 - Undertaken a full life cycle of mobile iOS Hybrid using Phonegap
- Application Development that includes testing on device and simulator as well.
- Having experience in developing hybrid applications in

- Phonegap and native plugin for hybrid applications.

 Having experience in Agile development methodology.

 Experienced in UX Design, can translate concept design into a user interface on mobiles like iPhone, iPad iPod
- Expertise in using Design patterns and object-oriented methodologies to design software for mobile phones.
- Experienced with Apple Approval Distribution Process, AdHoc Enterprise distribution.
- Experience of iPhone mobile application development and testing on device and simulator using x-code and Objective
- Involved in various parse level applications and well aware of parsing of SOAP, XML, and JSON formatted services for iPhone and iPad.
- Was involved in Usability testing of the application during early releases of the application to modify any user experience elements to be changed.
- Worked on various architectures such as MVC,MVVM,MVP,
- Singleton, Delegate and Notification patterns.KVC,KVO Experience of using version control and bug reporting tools like
- a clear case, clear quest, svn, TFS and git, etc. - Experience taking a project from scoping requirements through
- actual launch of application. - Knowledge of professional software engineering practices and best practices for the full software development life cycle, including coding standards, code reviews, source control
- management, build processes, testing, and operations.
 Experience providing prototypes / proofs-of-concept to the business content owners and users
- Experience in handling Web Services SOAP, XML, JSON RESTFUL.
 Worked on Core Data ability to write and troubleshoot SQLite
 Code and design managed Object context in objective C.
- Worked on the latest versions of iOS 13.0 and Xcode 11.0, well versed with latest changes in the industry.
- Experience in Mobile Application Development Frameworks Design Guidelines, design patterns and cross-platform tools like PhoneGap /Cordova/ react native.
- Experience in using writing web technologies for mobile, which includes advanced Javascript, HTML5, CSS3.

Personal Skills

Teamwork & collabration

Team lead / Technical lead/ Technical Project

Language Skill **English:**

- Reading/Writing (Good)
 Listening/Speaking (Not Good)

Vietnamese: Mother language

BIRTHDAY: 28/11/1989 EMAIL: b.x9.gaming@gm SKYPE: han.tran26 PHONE: 0973.474.602 . 19@gmail.com

Experience

Total years of Experience:

Ω

TECHNICAL MOBILE/PROJECT

9/2019 - Now:

Join pre-sales/ develop project, execute create requirement, design, coding, unit test, combination test, accept ion test for some customer on the world. 1/2019 - 9/2019

Freelancer an IOT APP for hungary/France customers

Design/Develop and owned ISubstudio APP with thousand users daily

SOTATEK

https://www.hydrelis.com/ https://isubstudio.wixsite.com/isubtitle

TECHNICAL LEADER MOBILE

7/2017 - 1/2019:

Join develop project, execute create requirement, design, coding, unit test, combination test, accept ion test for only Malaysia customer

TC System (Vietnam)

TECHNICAL LEADER IOS/MOBILE

31/2013 - 07/2017:

Join develop project, execute create requirement, design, coding, unit test, combination test, accept ion test for only Japan customer.

FPT Software Hanoi

SENIOR IOS/MAC/MOBILE DEVELOPER

03/2012 - 03/2013

Join develop project, execute create requirement, design, coding, unit test, combination test, accept ion test for only Japan customer.

Softfront Vietnam

IOS/WEB INTERN

05/2011 - 02/2012

LiviTalk..

Fude...

Join develop project, execute create requirement, design, coding, unit test, combination test, accept ion test for only Japan customer.

Telsoft Vietnam

Personezie Social Salon/Beauty shop Swagger codegen/Swift/RxSwift, RxCocoa/MVVM

Architecturina

Social Cashback Swift/KVO/MVMV Architecturing XS10 China Fitness Angular/Ionic/MVC Architecturing

Etiqa Smile (May Bank) Swift/RxSwift, RxCocoa/MVVM Architecturing

Diaital Marketplace IOS/Android/Anaular IS/ IOS/Ionic framework

Etiga Auto Assist Swift/RxSwift, RxCocoa/MVVM Architecturing

Swift/RxSwift, RxCocoa/MVVM Architecturing

Objective-C/MVC Architecturing

Iwinter Objective-c/MVC Architecturing

Objective-c/MVC Architecturing **I**speak

HBR IOS/Objective-c/MVC Architecturing Projects of FPT Software IOS/Objective-c/MVC Architecturing Projects of Telsoft IOS/Objective-c/MVC Architecturing

Projects of Sortfont Vietnam IOS/Objective-c/MVC Architecturing

Link of some APPs That's newest development:

1, develop a mobile app for Hitachi Japanese customer https://www.hitachi-solutions.com/credeon/

2, develop a mobile app for DOCOMO INC Japanese custo https://apps.apple.com/us/app/jspeak/id878880749

3, Full-stack developer for Salomee app https://apps.apple.com/us/app/salomee-%E3%82%B5%E3%83%AD%E3%83%9F%E3%83%BC/id1321899398 4, Make a Hybrid app for China custom

https://apps.apple.com/us/app/xs10-10%E5%91%A8%E5%8F%98%E8%BA%AB%E8%AE%A1%E5%88%92/id12

Education

2008 - 2012

Hanoi University of Technology

Bachelor of Information Technology (Software Engineering)